<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Juan Carlos Tovar</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/</link><description>Recent content on Juan Carlos Tovar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>History</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/history/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/history/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post History" />&lt;h2 id="consultant-at-red-hat-professional-services">&lt;strong>Consultant at Red Hat, Professional Services.&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h2>&lt;h3 id="summary">&lt;strong>Summary&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Working with focus in Automation, OpenShift, and GitOps technologies:&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Architect&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Advance Multicluster Management (ACM)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Argo CD&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Secrets management strategies using GitOps, AWS Secret Manager and External Secrets Operator&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Supporting New Hired graduates to get specific knowledge for the Technical Acount Management role&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Supporting new Graduates cohorts as Buddy &amp;amp; mentor&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>CNCF Cloud Native Iberia Ambassador&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Ansible developer&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Validated Patterns framework&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Working at long term Consulting Projects in Iberia and EMEA region&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;h3 id="cncf-iberia-organizer">&lt;strong>CNCF Iberia Organizer&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>(2023-Present)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cloud-consultant---red-hat">&lt;strong>Cloud Consultant - Red Hat&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>(2023-Present)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="technical-graduate---red-hat">&lt;strong>Technical Graduate - Red Hat&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>(2021-2022)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="stem-degree---telecommunications-engineering">&lt;strong>STEM degree - Telecommunications Engineering&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>(2015-2020)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contributions</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/contributions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/contributions/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/contributions/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Contributions" />&lt;h2 id="community-contributions">Community contributions
&lt;/h2>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Contribution&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Date&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Description&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Graphics&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Technical Blog - Share knowledge with a wider audience on the internet&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2024&lt;/td>
&lt;td>As one of my goals in 2024, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a blog page to upload content related to technical topics. In the commin month my plan is to make it grow &lt;a class="link" href="https://jtovarro.github.io/blog" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://jtovarro.github.io/blog&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>CNCF Ambassador&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Currently working to organize new CNCF events hosted in Madrid, our commitment as team is to share technical knowledge not only at Red Hat but beyond our frontiers. Let&amp;rsquo;s grow the community! Go to the official page to see upcomming events: &lt;a class="link" href="https://community.cncf.io/cloud-native-madrid-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://community.cncf.io/cloud-native-madrid-1/&lt;/a>. &lt;strong>Collaboration Teresa Giner, Alicia Maroto, Ricardo Noriega and colleagues from Solo.io and Suse.&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Community Valencia Twitch Meet-up&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Twitch Meet-Up: Secret Management following GitOps strategies. &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JxTJMqEoovQ&amp;amp;t=3259s" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Youtube Video&lt;/a>. &lt;strong>Collaboration Asier Cidón&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Lego Lab at Universitat Politecnica de Catalunya&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Introducing agile methodologies among UPC students using the class as space to play and learn. &lt;strong>Collaboration Ernesto Chacón and Jordi Olivé&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/lego.png"
width="1280"
height="960"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/lego_hu14527727450542095173.png 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/lego_hu11394958231900183983.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Universitat Politecnica - Lego Lab"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="133"
data-flex-basis="320px"
>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2019&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Bachellor Thesis associated with the Las Palmas de Gran Canaria Univeristy. Integration and optimization of ML and IA applications with Kubernetes: &lt;a class="link" href="https://accedacris.ulpgc.es/handle/10553/76839" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://accedacris.ulpgc.es/handle/10553/76839&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;h2 id="internal-contributions">Internal contributions
&lt;/h2>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Contribution&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Date&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Description&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Graphics&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Validated Patterns&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2024&lt;/td>
&lt;td>TO BE ADDED&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Iberia Meetup - Leapp and In-Place Upgrades talk&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2024&lt;/td>
&lt;td>In this session we will present our experience and some of the lessons learned at AXA (France). In this project we have worked from Consulting to facilitate, optimise and reduce human errors when updating their server fleet, using: Ansible to standardise and automate the upgrade process and Leapp as an upgrade tool; which allows us to benefit from the new features that RHEL has (and support), without the need to install new machines. &lt;a class="link" href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Bpy_Npp3iI0DH9k4nyLUak25sBqjY28H/view" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Session Reocrded&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Gymkhana facilitator - Graduation Program event at Brno&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Exported alongside the spanish 2021 cohort Alicia and Agustin the Gymkhana delivered in the Red Hat Summit Madrid to the graduation event that take place every year in Brno. We delivered this activity modified in terms of challenges and technologies to fit the attendants needs. The Gymkhana challenges and delivery was supreme as reported by the feedback requested. &lt;strong>Collaboration Alicia Maroto and Agustín Algorta&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Summit - Madrid&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Been the Red Hat team lead to the Gymkhana activity with our customers to facilitate one of the most attracting initiatives done in Iberia ever.&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/summit.png"
width="2048"
height="1365"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/summit_hu14787270344622786014.png 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/summit_hu3503716272262315416.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Summit 2023"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>EMEA TAM Mock Project&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Internal project to support the success of the EMEA Graduate Program. In this initiative we have been supporting the Technical Account Manager rotation for new cohorts with actions such as creating support cases and acting as &amp;ldquo;real customers&amp;rdquo;, so the Graduates could interact with support cases in Salesforce. And start to use TSE best practices while improving their technical skills at the same time: searching for KCS, documentation or even asking for help if they get stuck with the cases. All the documentation is in this &lt;a class="link" href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1fXCLU1W_lHC-B8cfQaNiPSDeA7SKPHIS" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>folder&lt;/a> and also a &lt;a class="link" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1JyOdtPmofik4hXpHI3vxvpshbuhgCxFYQPr7FH6RBSk/edit#responses" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>review&lt;/a> from the Graduates with 5/5 starts. &lt;strong>Collaboration Alicia Maroto and Agustín Algorta&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Solution published&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Compliance Operator rules kernel-module are FAILED after being APPLIED in OpenShift Container Platform 4: &lt;a class="link" href="https://access.redhat.com/solutions/6973351" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://access.redhat.com/solutions/6973351&lt;/a>. &lt;strong>Collaboration José Márquez&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Buddy&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Working closely to New Hirings, supporting them in everything they need at the begining of the journey. As buddy I tried to be as transparent as possible with my experience during my Graduate Program, provided tips, and together we try to get the best of the Graduate experience. Identifying when something is not going as expected and searching for mentors working in the area of New Hiring colleagues interest.&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;h2 id="sales-contributions">Sales contributions
&lt;/h2>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Contribution&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Date&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Description&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Graphics&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Open Tour Bilbao&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2024&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Managing the Edge with Ansible and RHEL OSTree demo speaker. &lt;strong>Collaboration with Luis Boubeta&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/edge.png"
width="1600"
height="1066"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/edge_hu17081862987777275028.png 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/edge_hu1135000866919712152.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Managing the Edge with AAP demo"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Quay at BBVA&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;a class="link" href="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1XoZuvzp72or_o-43IETURtU2M7TLXQJt2Wp2MHOCbJM/edit#slide=id.g252eb1d4225_0_9556" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Slides&lt;/a>. &lt;strong>Collaboration Miguel Ángel Saez, Carlos Cornejo&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Advanced Cluster Management couse delivered at Capgemini&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2023&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Explaining to app dev technical audience at High Potencial program in Capgemini about Cloud Computing benefits of using Advanced Cluster Management, to administrate the clusters fleet and deploy applications and policies the GitOps way. &lt;strong>Collaboration Luis Boubeta&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>WorkAthon at Red Hat Summit Connect Madrid&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Supporting this activity in the Summit Connect: reviewing laboratiories, and helping to both partners and customers during the activity day. Also colecting feedback and questions from customers to further analysis. &lt;strong>Supervision Moisés Rivera&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/workathon.jpg"
width="2048"
height="1365"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/workathon_hu10070979823689762102.jpg 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/workathon_hu3234220980235256331.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="WorkAthon at Summit 2022"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Middleware solutions&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Explaining to Grifols, a pharma customer, about Red Hat Middleware portfolio and its benefits. Link to the &lt;a class="link" href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1tnPelN4nLtPk2V4WilXTXQn6R604Qlpb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>vídeo&lt;/a> and &lt;a class="link" href="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1YGkT-_bzHopX1mwB8GnYG5rBaDCE83hkEbpHg3J3q3k/edit#slide=id.g12876cb2376_0_751" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>slides&lt;/a> used. &lt;strong>Collaboration Àngel Ollé&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Onsite AAP demo for Seidor Technicians&lt;/td>
&lt;td>2022&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Showing Red Hat partner in Zaragoza, Seidor, about new features included in Ansible Automation Platform v2.0. &lt;strong>Collaboration Moises Rivera&lt;/strong>&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/seidor.png"
width="1280"
height="960"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/seidor_hu8226013916921774707.png 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/contributions/seidor_hu16232043053075675159.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="AAP showcase"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="133"
data-flex-basis="320px"
>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/feedback/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="alba-gómez---technical-graduate">Alba Gómez - Technical Graduate
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Thank you for all the help and support during my first year at Red Hat. I really appreciate your confidence in me, giving me the opportunity to participe in real proyects to learn more about the day to day work.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Also, thank you for all the time you have spent teaching me new technologies, as well as getting me involved in calls with your team to meet more Red Hatters. I am sure you will achieve all your goals :)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="javier-león---consultant">Javier León - Consultant
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>I think Juan Carlos has made a huge progress since he started as a junior consultant and, in my opinion, he is far above of what you can expect from a junior.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From a skills perspective, he has developed a huge knowledge about Ansible, Openshift, Satellite and RHEL, but he also knows where you can find help when you need it, which is the same or more important. I started to work with him as my shadowee and he was exactly what you expect from a shadowee, humble, keeping attention and always asking or noting question for later.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I have also worked with him in a gig where he was working alone and I helped them a little bit with Satellite. He knows how to talk and manage clients which is not easy at all. He noted the questions that he didn&amp;rsquo;t know about and tried to help them in every area they needed, even when it wasn&amp;rsquo;t his area of expertise and he needed to look for help. He is capable of carrying solo gigs without issues, an achievement to be proud of for someone who has been working in consulting for a year.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Besides, the best part of him is his attitude, you can tell from the first moment that he is eager to learn new things, he is always studying some certificate or new courses, reaching out to colleagues when he is in PD and trying to find out if there is anything interesting he can learn or help with.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To recap, he just have to continue working like he is doing right now, be a bit brave when facing new challenges and gain some experience because that is the only thing he lacks of.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="iván-aragones---senior-consultant">Iván Aragones - Senior Consultant
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Thanks for your great work automating the IPU processes. It&amp;rsquo;s been a great base to be used in other similar projects. Awesome!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="fran-garcia---principal-consultant">Fran Garcia - Principal Consultant
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Juan Carlos has provided an excellent delivery in the AXA RHEL modernization project, first of a kind project done in the region. His guidance and patience towards a challenging project has driven it to success!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="adonis-garcia---consultant">Adonis Garcia - Consultant
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>I just have good words to evaluate the work that Juan Carlos is doing in AXA. He just needed a few days of shadowing to take care of the project like he has been leading it from the beginning. I was so surprise how Juan Carlos learned new technologies in a short period of time and his capacity to gain customer’s trust.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He’s able to manage issues and challenges by himself even though he didn’t have expertise in some areas. That`s one of the best skills he can have as a consultant.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’m pretty sure he’s gonna be soon one of our references in consulting. Nothing important to say as improvements, just keep pushing as until now and try to focus your carrer in what you want in order to be a referent person in some technologies/areas.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ángel-ollè---specialist-solution-architect">Ángel Ollè - Specialist Solution Architect
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Having mentored in different cycles and opportunities here at the company, I can confidently say that Juan Carlos has demonstrated exceptional competencies and behaviors since joining us. Juan Carlos embodies the majority of the MULTIPLIER behaviors in a comprehensive manner, from connecting with others to collaborating effectively. Additionally, Juan Carlos has shown great influencing skills, being an attentive listener and exhibiting a strong commitment to the milestones presented in the pre-sales phase. Their perseverance is noteworthy, always looking out for the best interests of the team. Juan Carlos possesses excellent problem-solving abilities, customer interaction skills, and adds critical thinking to their repertoire, making them a strong candidate for any department. They are truly a person that any team would be fortunate to have on their roster.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Juan Carlos has demonstrated the ability to accompany us in client meetings and provide valuable feedback. They have also consistently fulfilled all the commitments that were set, including, in my opinion, something very important: taking the initiative to commit and deliver to the client, while maintaining high quality in their work. Juan Carlos has actively participated in internal team meetings, focusing on the team&amp;rsquo;s goals and transferring their competence and ease to all members. When assigned tasks, he shown the capacity to resolve them and drive them forward. Juan Carlos has proven their ability to research and document, consistently going above and beyond by providing an extra mile of quality in their work.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He has greatly contributed to effective collaboration within the team, fostering a positive and productive work environment. He consistently seeks feedback and actively incorporates it into their work, displaying a growth mindset and a continuous desire to improve. He shown remarkable adaptability, quickly learning new technologies and processes, which has been invaluable in navigating complex projects and delivering exceptional results. Also, he&amp;rsquo;s consistently demonstrate a high level of professionalism, displaying a positive and respectful attitude towards colleagues and clients alike.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He shown a genuine passion for their work, consistently demonstrating enthusiasm and dedication that inspires those around them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Learning</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/learning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/p/learning/</guid><description>&lt;p>Explore all the listed certifications validated in &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.credly.com/users/jtovarro" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Credly.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="red-hat-certifications">Red Hat Certifications
&lt;/h2>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Certification&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Date issued&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Building Resilient Microservices with Istio and Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh&lt;/td>
&lt;td>March 2024&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Architect (RHCA)&lt;/td>
&lt;td>March 2023&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Specialist in OpenShift Application Developer&lt;/td>
&lt;td>March 2023&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Specialist in MultiCluster Management&lt;/td>
&lt;td>January 2023&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Specialist in contanariezed applications&lt;/td>
&lt;td>October 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Open Library Practices - TL500 in London&lt;/td>
&lt;td>July 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Engineer&lt;/td>
&lt;td>July 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified Specialist in OpenShift Administration&lt;/td>
&lt;td>May 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Red Hat Certified System Administrator&lt;/td>
&lt;td>January 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/learning/rhca.png"
width="125"
height="125"
srcset="https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/learning/rhca_hu345886534622303889.png 480w, https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/cv/p/learning/rhca_hu3491215013830803578.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="RHCA"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="100"
data-flex-basis="240px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="other-trainings-and-certifications">Other Trainings and Certifications
&lt;/h2>&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Certification&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Date issued&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Fundamentals for Istio by Solo.io&lt;/td>
&lt;td>March 2023&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Microsoft Azure Fundamentals&lt;/td>
&lt;td>December 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>GitOps at Scale by CodeFresh&lt;/td>
&lt;td>October 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>GitOps Fundamentals by CodeFresh&lt;/td>
&lt;td>April 2022&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;h2 id="soft-skills-trainings">Soft Skills Trainings
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Soft Skills courses represent a total of 40 hours approximately.&lt;/p>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Certification&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>7 Habits of Highly Effective People (vILT)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Giving and Receiving Feedback from Associates (vILT)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>5 Choices to Extraordinary Productivity (vILT)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Development Beyond Learning (DBL) courses&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Careers Journeys (vILT)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Communicating with Virtual Presence (vILT)&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>Links</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/links/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtovarro.github.io/cv/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>